A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1966
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr.-President (3 folders), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
  - Hardy, J.E.-Director of Student Housing, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare-Department of, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Heat and Power- C.F. DeBusk and C.C. McCoy, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Highway Department, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Insurance Adjusters, John Roane, Incorporated, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - J/K Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Justice, Glen- International Business Machines(IBM), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - King, Howard P., Director of Dining Halls, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Land Grant Colleges-National Association of State Universities, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Laundry-Director, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Library, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr.-President (3 folders), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 19-21)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Magill House, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Marion College (2 folders), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 25-26)
  - Military-Commandment, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Military-ROTC, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - P- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Power and Heat, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations, R. Craig Fabian-Director (4 folders), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34-37)
  - Q-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Research Park Development (2 folders), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 40-41)
  - Row, Stuart B.-Director of Community Colleges and Extension Programs (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Publications and News-Warren Strother and Jenks Robertson, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers (SACUBO), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Salary, Faculty, 1965-1966 Information, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Classified Personnel Salary Adjustments, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Shanks, Fred O. – Manager, Printing Department, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Space-Office, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Self Study (4 folders), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
  - Sowder, Allen- Attorney, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Attorney-State, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, J. Gordon Bennett, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Comptroller, Sidney C. Day Jr., 1966 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Budget, Division of L.M. Kuhn, Director, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Council of Higher Education (2 folders), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
  - Industrial Development and Planning, Division of, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Personnel-Division of, John W. Garber, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Property Records and Insurance-Bureau of, Stewart R. Moore, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Purchases and Supplies-Division of, G. Lloyd Nunnally, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Records Administrator, State-G.R. Yarlott (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Technical Education-Department of, Dr. Dana B. Hamel, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Treasury-Department of, Frank B. Miller, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Statement of Revenue Other than from Appropriations, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-01-31 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-02-28 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-03-31 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-04-30 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-05-31 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-07-31 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-08-31 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-09-30 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Governor, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-10-31 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-11-30 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-12-31 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Student Aid Association, H.H. McEver, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Student Correspondence, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Student Tuition Plan-Payment and Collection, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - T- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Traffic and Parking Study (2 folders), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Tech Festival, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Technical Services, State, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Upward Bound Program, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - V-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.I. - Planning Engineer, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Water Authority, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - XYZ- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Purchasing Agent, Swink H.W., 1966 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Highway Department, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1966-03-31 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- 1967
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Admissions- Reports, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Agronomy Department, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Animal Husbandry Department, Mr. George Litton, Head, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Architect's Collaborative Incorporated, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - B- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Bank Correspondence, General, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Blanket Letters, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Boone House, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Brandt, Warren W., Vice President Academic Affairs, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Budget-Local, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Budget Material, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - S.K. Cassell-Personal, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Clifton Forge- Covington Branch, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Development Council, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Dormitory Questionnaires, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Hahn, Dr. T. Marshall, Jr.- President (3 folders), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 36-38)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr. #2- President (3 folders), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 39-41)
  - I- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - J-K Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - L- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lunsford Sons and Izard, Chas. (2 folders), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Marion College (2 folders), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Final Accounting-McCormick Memorial, 1957-01-25 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Military- Commandment, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Military-ROTC, Army and Air Force, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Nickols, I.E.- Security Director, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Herman Pritchard-Director Alumni Associations, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Power Plant, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - P- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - S- Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
  - Row, Dr. S.B. – Director of Community Colleges, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - R. Stuart Royer and Associates, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Shirk, Frank C-Librarian, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Shotts, James L. – Purchasing Agent, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Strother, Warren H.- Director of Information Services, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Monthly Statement of Revenues other than from Appropriations, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-01-31 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-05-31 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-02-28 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-03-31 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-04-30 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-07-31 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-08-31 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-09-30 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-10-31 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-11-30 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1967-12-31 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Sterrett, William M.-Director, Buildings and Grounds (2 folders), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Aid Association, H.M. McEver- Secretary, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Student Correspondence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tech Festival, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - YMCA(Young Men's Christian Association), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Student Government Association-Senate, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.I, Director-Physical Plant Planning (4 folders), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 11-14)
  - XYZ-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Council-University (4 folders), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 17-20)
  - Commencement Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Research Council, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Tech Festival, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Bull, Dean Fred W.-Graduate School, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Dean Joseph G.-Dean of Men (2 folders), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 28-29)
  - Executive Committee-VPI Board of Visitors, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Bell, Dean Wilson B.- Agriculture, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Dean, Dean James W.-Dean of Students (4 folders), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 32-33, Box 26, Box-folder 1-2)
  - Burchard, Dean Charles H. – Architecture, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Students- Reports, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Harder, Dean Martha B.- Dean of Women, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Harper, Dean Laura J. –Home Economics, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Harrison, Dean W.B.-Research Division (2 folders), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
  - Lacy, Dean M.P. – Admissions and Records, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Malpass, Dean Leslie F.- Arts and Sciences, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, Dean Herbert H.- Commerce, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Skelton, Dean W.E. – Extension Division, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Worchester, Dean Willis G.- Engineering, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Boone, J.F.-Treasurer, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Burke, Carl E.-Chief Accountant, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Butt, Albin T.-Director of Personnel, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Cato, William H.- Director of Placement, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Evans, E.B. – Business Manager, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Fabian, R. Craig- Director of Development, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Hardy, J.E. Director of Student Housing, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Whitney L.- Director Computing Center (2 folders), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21-22)
  - Moseley, Frank O.- Director Computing Center, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Director of Auxiliary Enterprises and University Services (2 folders), 1967 (Box 68, Folder 4-5a)
  - Sewage Collection and Treatment, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- 1968
  - Building Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Senate Sterring Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Student Activities Committee (3 folders), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 29-31)
  - Traffic Committee, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - University Council (8 folders), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 33-37, Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - University Council, Part 2 (6 folders), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 4-9)
  - Brown, Dean J. Gordon-Dean of Men (3 folders), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
  - Bull, Dean Fred W.-Graduate School, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Council of Deans, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Burchard, Dean Charles H. – Architect, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Dr. J. W. Dean-Vice President Student Affair (2 folders), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
  - Dean, Dean James W.-Dean of Students (3 folders), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 18-20)
  - Harder, Dean Martha B.- Dean of Women, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Harper, Dean Laura-Home Economics, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Lacy, Dean M.P.- Admissions and Records, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Mitchell, Dean H.H.-College of Business, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Skelton, Dean W.E.- Extension Division, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Worcester, Dean Willis G.- Engineering, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Bell, Dean Wilson B. – Development (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Burke, Carl E.- Chief Accountant, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Butt, Albin T.- Director of Personnel, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Cato, W.H.-Director of Placement, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Hardy, J.E.- Director of Student Housing, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Evans, E.B.- Business Manager, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Harrison, Dean W.B.- Research Division, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, Whitney L., Director- Computer Center (3 folders), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 35-36, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Dr. J.R. Montgomery- Institutional Research, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Martin, James E. –Agriculture, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Malpass, Dean Leslie F.- Arts and Sciences, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - King, H.P., Jr., Director- Dining Halls, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Moseley, F.O., Director Athletic Association, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Nickols, I.E.-Director of Security, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Russell, G.E.- Director Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Shirk, Frank C. Librarian, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Shotts, James L. – Purchasing Agent, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Sterrett, William M.- Buildings and Grounds (2 folders), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - Strother, Warren H.- Information Services, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Master Plan Report, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C.- Physical Plant Planning, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Art Commission, Floyd E. Johnson, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Attorney General-Virginia, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts-Joe James, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Department of Community Colleges-Dr. Dana B. Hamel, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller- Sidney C. Day Jr., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - State Council of Higher Education- Dr. Prince B. Woodard, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Division of Budget- L.M. Kuhn, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - State Highway Department, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Governor, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Division of Personnel- John W. Garber, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Department of Purchases and Supply- G. Lloyd Nunnally, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Property Records and Insurance- Stewart R. Moore, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings- H.D. Hamner, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System- Charles H. Smith, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - State Board of Education, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - State Corporation Commission, Division of Aeronautics, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Department of Treasury- Lewis H. Vaden, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Office, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Applications (3 folders), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 35-37)
  - B- Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 38-39)
  - Blanket Letters, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Board of Visitors, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Brandt, Dr. Warren W., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - C and P Telephone Cables, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - C- Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 44-45)
  - Cassell, S.C.- Personal, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Civilian Interdorm Council, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Club Officers, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - D- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Donaldson Brown Continuing Education Center, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Economic Stabilization Task Group-Price Stabilization Operation, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Federal Programs/Grants, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, Sub Committee-University Council, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Gifts-Grants, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - H- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Marshall T. Hahn Jr. (9 folders), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 15-23)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Hokie Club, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - K- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Kidder, Peabody, and Company, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - L- Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 29-30)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard (2 folders), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 31-32)
  - Mc- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Manual Operating Policies and Procedures, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Marion College (2 folders), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 36-37)
  - Metropolitan Areas Study Commission, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Military-Army and Air Force, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Mitchell, Petty, and Shetterly, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Liquid Nitrogen Tank, Addition to Physics Building, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Overtime, Authorized, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Alfred C. Payne, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Physics Department, Bailey Meter Company- Nuclear Information, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Research Corporation, Caribbean Canadian Chemical Co, S.A., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Bonds, Student Center Fee (3 folders), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
  - Revenue Bonds, Dorms and Dining Halls (2 folders), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
  - S- Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Salary Adjustments- Non Faculty (1966-1967, 1967-1968), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Scholarships, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Roger L.- Director, State Technical Services (3 folders), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 23-25)
  - Allen Sowder, Attorney, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Student Correspondence, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Student Government Association Senate (2 folders), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 28-29)
  - Student Union Board, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Tech Festival, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Sanitation Authority (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-01-31 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-02-02 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-03-31 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-04-30 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-05-31 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-06-30 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-07-31 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-08-31 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-09-30 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-10-31 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-11-30 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1968-12-31 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Water Authority, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Student Aid Association, H.H. McEver, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Wills, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - YMCA, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Traffic and Parking Improvement Program-UNC Chapel Hill (2 folders), 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises and University Services (2 folders), 1968 (Box 68, Folder 5b-6)
- 1969
  - Summer Conferences, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Extension Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Building Committee (2 folders), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
  - Commencement Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate Steering Committee (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Forums Board, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Library Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Student Activities Committee (2 folders), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 24-25)
  - Traffic Committee, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Student Affairs, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Studies- Commission on, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - University Council, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Council of Deans, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - University Council (7 folders), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 31-37)
  - Brandt, W.W.- Executive Vice President, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Brown, J. Gordon, Dean- Student Services (2 folders), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 39-40)
  - Bull, Fred W.- Graduate School, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Burchard, C.H. – Architecture, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Dean, J.W. – Vice President, Student Affairs (8 folders), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 43-45, Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Harder, Martha B.- Dean, Men and Women's Residence Programs, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Harper, G.M.- Arts and Sciences, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Harper, Laura J.- Home Economics, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Lacy, M.P. – Admissions and Records, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Lavery, W.E.-Vice President of Finance, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - McKeefery, W.J.- Executive Vice President, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Malpass, L.F.- Vice President of Academic Affairs, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Martin, J.E.- Agriculture, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell, H.H.- College of Business, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Skelton, W.E.- Extension, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Worcester, W.G.-Engineering, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Bell, Wilson B.- Development, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Boone, J.F. – Treasurer, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Burke, Carl E.- Chief Accountant, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Butt, A.T.- Personal, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Cato, W.H.- Placement, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Evans, E.B.- Business Manager, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Hardy, J.E.- Student Housing, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 23)